♪I lament on the cruel and untimely love♪
أنا أتحسر على الحب القاسي والغير أوانه ♪
♪Yet I come to realise it's a daydream when the bubbles burst♪
♪ ومع ذلك أدركت أنه حلم يقظة عندما تنفجر الفقاعات ♪
♪A city of spring flowers♪
♪ مدينة زهور الربيع ♪
♪Sinks into the indifferent autumnal frost♪
♪ يغرق في الصقيع الخريفي غير المبال
♪A snowflake falls into the river♪
♪ تسقط ندفة ثلجية في النهر ♪
♪The biting cold stalks over♪
♪ البرد القارص ينبع
♪All assumptions are nothing♪
كل الافتراضات لا شيء
♪But a disguised makeup♪
♪ لكن مكياج مقنع
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the passionate gaze behind the mask♪
♪ للنظرة العاطفية خلف القناع ♪
♪Love and hate are the most unforgettable feelings♪
الحب والكراهية من أكثر المشاعر التي لا تنسى
♪Overwhelmed by my longings♪
غارقة في شوقي ♪
♪I tear off those old scores♪
♪ مزقت تلك الدرجات القديمة ♪
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the irretrievable past♪
إلى الماضي الذي لا يمكن استرجاعه ♪
=Little Mad Doctor=
= الطبيب المجنون الصغير =
=Episode 26=
= الحلقة 26 =
How could a woman who goes against norms
كيف يمكن لامرأة تتعارض مع الأعراف
and causes trouble to the court
ويسبب مشاكل للمحكمة
be qualified as the empress?
تكون مؤهلة لتكون الإمبراطورة؟
If my father and brother were to know about this,
إذا كان والدي وأخي على علم بهذا ،
they will seek justice for me
سيطلبون العدل من أجلي
by charging an attack on you with the entire military force.
بشن هجوم عليك بكل القوة العسكرية.
Princess Jinghong has gone mad.
جن جنون الأميرة جينغ هونغ.
Men.
رجال.
Send her to the Imperial Academy of Physicians.
أرسلها إلى الأكاديمية الإمبراطورية للأطباء.
Why are you so anxious, Your Majesty?
لماذا أنت قلق جدا يا جلالة الملك؟
Are you trying to hush up me?
هل تحاول إسكاتي؟
I will make a bet with you.
سأراهن معك.
If I can't live through tomorrow,
إذا لم أستطع العيش غدًا ،
the regime of Shang
نظام شانغ
won't sustain before next year.
لن تستمر قبل العام المقبل.
You...
أنت...
Jinghong.
جينغهونغ.
Would you rather die
هل تفضل الموت
than marry me?
من الزواج بي؟
She's my woman.
إنها امرتي.
How dare you lay fingers on her?
كيف تجرؤ على وضع أصابعك عليها؟
I shall see
سأرى
who forced my consort
الذي أجبر رفيقي
to marry another man.
للزواج من رجل آخر.
My Lord.
ربي.
They've bullied me.
لقد قاموا بتخويفي.
Jinghong.
جينغهونغ.
Never fear, Jinghong.
لا تخف أبدا ، جينغهونغ.
I don't intend to kill anymore
لا أنوي القتل بعد الآن
and I'm sick
وانا مريض
of violence.
من العنف.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
I just want
انا فقط اريد
to lead a peaceful life with Jinghong.
لقيادة حياة سلمية مع جينغهونغ.
I'm willing to hand over the military power
أنا على استعداد لتسليم القوة العسكرية
as well as
إلى جانب
the Internal Activities Depot.
مستودع الأنشطة الداخلية.
Longyuan,
لونجيوان ،
this is unconvincing though.
هذا غير مقنع بالرغم من ذلك.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Longyuan is devious.
لونجيوان مخادع.
Don't let him fool you.
لا تدعه يخدعك.
I've already figured out
لقد اكتشفت بالفعل
that the Blood Curse in me
أن لعنة الدم بداخلي
was done by you.
تم القيام به بواسطتك.
What an ambitious empress you are.
يا لك من إمبراطورة طموحة.
Not only did you own a secretive troop,
لم يكن لديك فقط قوات سرية ،
I also discovered
اكتشفت أيضا
that you have close associates from all the empires
أن لديك شركاء مقربون من جميع الإمبراطوريات
colluding behind the scene.
التآمر وراء الكواليس.
The Empress
الامبراطورة
has everything in her control now.
كل شيء تحت سيطرتها الآن.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Don't listen to him.
لا تستمع إليه.
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Lord War is trying to create confusion.
يحاول اللورد وور خلق البلبلة.
This is unforgivable.
هذا أمر لا يغتفر.
That's right.
صحيح.
Lord War's lying
الكذب اللورد الحرب
to get everyone confused. Men.
لإرباك الجميع.  رجال.
Take Lord War down.
اقضِ على Lord War.
Insolent!
وقح!
Empress.
الإمبراطورة.
I seem to underestimate you.
يبدو أني أقلل من شأنك.
Do you really think
هل تعتقد حقا
I'm that incompetent?
أنا غير كفؤ إلى هذا الحد؟
I'm well aware
أنا على علم جيد
of what you've done
لما قمت به
since a long time ago.
منذ زمن طويل.
Longyuan managed to eliminate all the betrayers this time.
تمكنت Longyuan من القضاء على جميع الخونة هذه المرة.
I shall thank you for your army.
سوف أشكرك على جيشك.
The empress's power
قوة الإمبراطورة
has grown immensely.
نمت بشكل هائل.
Longyuan,
لونجيوان ،
do you have the confidence
هل لديك الثقة
to secretly eliminate them completely?
للقضاء عليها سرًا تمامًا؟
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
I will do my best.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي.
If you manage to overcome this
إذا تمكنت من التغلب على هذا
for Shang,
لشانغ ،
I will grant
سأمنح
anything you ask for
أي شيء تطلبه
even if
حتى لو
you want
انت تريد
to ascend
للصعود
to the throne.
على العرش.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
I've never thought
لم افكر ابدا
of taking the throne.
من أخذ العرش.
All I wish is a peaceful world
كل ما أتمناه هو عالم يسوده السلام
and the people thrive.
والناس يزدهرون.
Someone once told me
قال لي أحدهم ذات مرة
that she wished for a world where everyone is born equal
أنها تتمنى عالمًا يولد فيه الجميع متساوين
and doesn't need to bow down to oppressive powers.
ولا داعي للخضوع للقوى القمعية.
Everyone can live with dignity.
يمكن للجميع العيش بكرامة.
I also believe in this wish.
أنا أيضا أؤمن بهذه الرغبة.
Everyone is born equal?
يولد الجميع متساوين؟
Do you know
هل تعرف
it can be really hard to achieve?
يمكن أن يكون من الصعب حقًا تحقيقه؟
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
after
بعد
I subdue the riots,
أخضعت أعمال الشغب ،
please allow me
رجاء اسمح لي
to live in seclusion
للعيش في عزلة
and lead a peaceful life
ويعيشون حياة سلمية
together with Jinghong.
مع جينغهونغ.
Father.
أب.
You can't do this to Mother.
لا يمكنك فعل هذا لأمي.
Back off.
تراجع.
You're in no place to speak here.
أنت لست في مكان للتحدث هنا.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Please don't believe him.
من فضلك لا تصدقه.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
My Lord.
ربي.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
My Lord,
ربي،
here's the antidote.
ها هو الترياق.
I've made it for you.
لقد صنعته من أجلك.
♪Time slips by in that dream-like world. Life is always full of splendor♪
♪ الوقت يمر في هذا العالم الذي يشبه الحلم.  الحياة دائما مليئة بالروعة ♪
♪We part when the flowers fall♪
♪ نفترق عندما تسقط الأزهار
♪Desolate chills blow away several autumns♪
♪ قشعريرة مقفرة تهب عدة خريفات ♪
Your credits are full.
الاعتمادات الخاصة بك ممتلئة.
Mission completed.
المهمة اكتملت.
You're returning to the real world.
أنت تعود إلى العالم الحقيقي.
Am I leaving now?
هل سأرحل الآن؟
I didn't expect
لم أتوقع
this day
هذا اليوم
would arrive so soon.
سيصل قريبا جدا.
My Lord.
ربي.
I wish to see more of this world.
أتمنى أن أرى المزيد من هذا العالم.
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد
(The principle of sterility during surgery is)
(مبدأ العقم أثناء الجراحة)
(Is this a dream?)
(أهذا حلم؟)
Do you know the answer to this question,
هل تعرف الجواب على هذا السؤال ،
students?
طلاب؟
Chu Jinghong.
تشو جينغهونغ.
Do you?
هل أنت؟
(The end.)
(النهاية.)
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد
♪Hair turns grey in one winter night♪
♪ يتحول لون الشعر إلى اللون الرمادي في ليلة شتاء ♪
♪The appearance remains in spite of the thick frost♪
المظهر يبقى بالرغم من الصقيع الكثيف
♪Time slips by in that dream-like world♪
♪ الوقت يمر في هذا العالم الذي يشبه الحلم
♪Life is always full of splendor♪
♪ الحياة دائما مليئة بالروعة
♪We part when the flowers fall♪
♪ نفترق عندما تسقط الأزهار
♪Desolate chills blow away several autumns♪
♪ قشعريرة مقفرة تهب عدة خريفات ♪
♪Eternal love is all I seek♪
الحب الأبدي هو كل ما أسعى إليه
♪Though the sweet dream fades at last♪
رغم أن الحلم الجميل يتلاشى أخيرًا ♪
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد